ARJUN NASKAR

650.575.3251 anaskar@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/arjunnaskar

ABOUT ME

A demand generation, lifecycle, and marketing ops professional with 12+ years of experience across B2C and B2B tech companies. Looking for a senior marketing position where I can make the most impact.

Soft Skills	Hard Skills	Software	
People management	Forecasting & planning	Google Suite	
Hiring & recruiting	Demand generation	Salesforce	
Strong presentation &	Product marketing Marketo & Bra		
communication experience	Sales & marketing ops	Mode & Looker	
	Analytics: SQL, Excel	Outreach	

EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder, StandardCode (YC Summer 2021)

May 2021 - May 2022

Founded StandardCode and went through the Summer 2021 batch of Y Combinator. We focused on creating an API that helped companies comply with COPPA and other child data privacy laws globally. We successfully raised a \$2MM+ seed round and had a few beta customers before pivoting. We explored other ideas including a financial savings product for teens as well as a tool for Customer Success and Sales to be faster at outbound prospecting.

Head of B2B Marketing, Remind

December 2015 - May 2021

Started as a Senior Product Marketing Manager working on our first monetization efforts. Responsibilities included positioning, branding, GTM launch, and pricing. Once one of the products started gaining traction, I focused on building a team and process around GTM for our enterprise offering. Responsibilities included building and scaling a demand generation engine, hiring and training our first SDRs, BDRs, and account executives, developing lifecycle marketing, and building our marketing and sales ops infrastructure. Grew from \$0 to \$20MM ARR.

Growth & Product Projects

February 2015 - December 2015

Worked on side projects that scaled to a few thousand users. HireReady was the common app for the gig economy. Clients included Homejoy, Flour & Water, Kokio food truck. Stork was a text-based Q&A service for expecting parents to connect with doulas, nurses, and lactation consultants.

Growth Manager, Homejoy

December 2012 - February 2015

Joined Homejoy as the 2nd full-time employee. Started out as a city launcher, growing supply and demand in each of the first 20 U.S. markets before hiring a team to open the rest. Transitioned to a growth position where I created our lifecycle and retention programs for our demand and supply side using Oracle's Responsys. Launched 30 markets in 18 months.

Business Development Manager, Nutraclick

January 2010 - September 2012

Owned the P&L for one of Nutraclick's flagship brands, Force Factor. Responsibilities included supply chain management, product development, and contract negotiations with GNC, Bodybuilding.com, Walmart, and Walgreens. Launched 5 products with online and in-store distribution from formulation to promotion.

EDUCATION	Alum	Bachelor of Science
	Y Combinator	Computational Biology
	Summer '21	Massachusetts Institute of Technology

REFERENCES